Revenge gets ugly.
Jonah Hex is a action, western, drama film directed by Jimmy Hayward.
Gunslinger Jonah Hex is appointed by President Ulysses Grant to track down terrorist Quentin
Turnbull, a former Confederate officer determined on unleashing hell on earth.
Jonah not only secures freedom by accepting this task, he also
gets revenge on the man who slew his wife and child.
Jonah Hex, played by Josh Brolin.
Turnbull, played by John Malkovich.
Leila, played by Megan Fox.
Burke, played by Michael Fassbender.
Lieutenant Grass, played by Will Arnett.
Ulysses S. Grant, played by Aidan Quinn.
Jonah Hex is a 2010 American Western superhero film based on
the DC Comics character of the same name.
Directed by Jimmy Hayward (in his live-action debut) from a screenplay by Neveldine/Taylor, the film stars Josh Brolin in
the title role, alongside John Malkovich, Megan Fox, Michael Fassbender, Will Arnett and Michael Shannon.
Produced by Legendary Pictures, Andrew Lazar's Mad Chance Productions and Akiva Goldsman's
Weed Road Pictures, the film was released on June 18, 2010, by Warner Bros.
It was a commercial failure, having grossed only $11
million against a budget of $47 million.
It received generally negative reviews from critics.
The film explores themes of gunslinger, hell, comic
book, based on comic, facial scar.
The tone is emotional and intense.